

Borja Alonso Melero

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Executive Summary

I am a software developer. My knowledge and experience in software development allows me to produce quality software to solve any type of problem that comes in my way

Areas of Expertise

- · Mobile app development (Android, multiplatform)
- · Ionic Framework
- Android
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- . CSS
- Node IS
- AngularJS
- Web applications
- WordPress
- Webflow

Reach me at:

- Phone: +34665987324
- E-mail: borialonso95@amail.com
- · LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/borjaalonso-melero-391945120/

Languages:

· Spanish: native

• English: C1

• French: B1

• Catalan: B2

Hobbies:

- Windsurf
- Tennis
- Music
- Football
- Padel
- Technology

Soft skills:

- Polite
- Adventurous
- Ambitious
- Rational
- Sincere

Work Experience

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Partner & CO-Founder of Journify May 2017 - Sep 2021

- Enterpreunership project
- Development of a hybrid application for mobile devices
- Development of a dashboard in Angular + TailwindCSS

WAITER

May 2014 - April 2018

- Worked in several restaurants such as Masia Rocafort and Maxia Xamandreu
- Also worked as bartender at La BibliotecaBar and Loco Club.

PRIVATE TEACHER

May 2015 - Feb 2021

- Teacher of maths, physics, chemistry and english to several students with learning problems in high school. 10h/week
- Windsurf instructor in Denia (Alicante) to boys and girls between 9 and 20 years old during summer holidays

Education & Training

UNIVERSITAT POLITÈCNICA DE VALÈNCIA (UPV)

Degree in computer engineering (2013-2019)

- Specialized in software development
- Worked in lots of group projects during the degree
- Combined it with my entrepreneurship project

EDELWEISS HIGH SCHOOL

September 2000 - May 2010 Bilingual school

- Bilingual school where I studied until the age of 15

Personal experiences

- I went to Cape Town (South Africa) to do some voluntary work for 3 weeks. What we did was to teach the children of Hangberg (the community we were focused on) to make them see there is another way of life.
- Long stays in London to improve my English